Guide to the Charles Barsotti Accessions
The Wittliff Collections
Charles Barsotti Accessions
1915-2018
1960-2010
The Wittliff Collections https://www.thewittliffcollections.txstate.edu
Barsotti, Charles C. (1933-2014)
UPWC.18064
15 Linear Feet
15.5 boxes
Multiple accessions documenting the career of Texas State University alumnus and internationally recognized cartoonist, Charles Barsotti. Materials include original drawings, correspondence, files relating to marketing campaigns, and magazines featuring his work.
Conditions Governing Access
Collection is open for research.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gifts of Ramoth Barsotti, 2010-2018
Biographical Note
Charles Barsotti was born in San Marcos, Texas in 1933 and grew up in San Antonio. He graduated from Texas State University in 1955 before serviing in the Army. He later worked at the Brown School in San Marcos, a residential treatment center for people with special needs while studying with the aim of obtaining a master's degree in education.
Barsotti was the cartoon editor of The Saturday Evening Post and a staff cartoonist at The New Yorker beginning in 1970. His work also appeared in Playboy, Punch and Fast Company, among other publications. In 1992, his dog character was adopted as a logo by the office supplies company Niceday Ltd, which was taken over the French company Guilbert, leading to the nickname "Niceday pup" in the United Kingdom
Barsotti died of brain cancer on June 16, 2014, at his home in Kansas City, Missouri, aged 80.
Scope and Contents
Multiple accessions documenting the career of Texas State University alumnus and internationally recognized cartoonist, Charles Barsotti. Materials include original drawings, correspondence, files relating to marketing campaigns, and magazines featuring his work.
Index Terms
Subjects
Advertising; Cartoonists -- United States; Cartoons and comics; Commercial art
Subjects (Corporations)
Saturday Evening Post; New Yorker (New York, N.Y.)
- Accession 2010-132
  Abstract
  One cartoon by Charles Barsotti.
  - One Charles Barsotti cartoon, matted. Quote reads "This here is a number I wrote when I recovered a hidden memory" (Map-case Dr. 23)
- Accession 2018-022
  48 cartoons from the New Yorker magazine created by Charles Barsotti, June 21, 1969-October 24, 1977.
  - 48 cartoons from New Yorker magazine by Charles Barsotti, June 21, 1969-October 24, 1977 (Box 2472, Folder 21)
- Accession 2018-023
  Donation by Ramoth Barsotti of Charles Barsotti's correspondence with Southwest Texas State University and Dick Holland, including a mark up draft of introduction by Billy Porterfield to Barsotti's Texas, 1984-2013.
  - Correspondence between Barsotti and Southwest Texas State University and Dick Holland, including marked up draft of introduction by Bill Porterfield to Barsotti's Texas, 1984-2003 (Box 2472, Folder 22)
- Accession 2018-064
  A collection of donated items from Ramoth Barsotti displaying cartoons that have been created by Charles Barsotti. The drawings can be seen in The Saturday Evening Post. The collection also includes newspaper articles, clippings, and correspondence, 1915-2015. The folder titles preceding a semicolon reflect Barsotti's original descriptions.
  - "SW Texas"; Correspondence to Barsotti from Texas State alumni association, and a fifties decade reunion alumni directory list, 1987-2015 (Box 2782, Folder 1)
  - "Miscellaneous High School and College"; Original cartoon drawings and clippings, correspondence, and copies of newspaper articles, 1952-1991 (Box 2782, Folder 2)
  - "Southwest Texas"; Copies of articles, and correspondence to Barsotti from Richard and Dick Holland, 1990-2005 (Box 2782, Folder 3)
  - "S.W.T. President's Award"; invitations, newspapers, brochures, and correspondence, 1987-2004 (Box 2782, Folder 4)
  - "SW Texas"; correspondence, and a Texas State distinguish student booklet, 1986-2012 (Box 2782, Folder 5)
  - "Advisory Council"; Wittliff magazines, correspondence, and brochures, 1987-2009 (Box 2782, Folder 6)
  - "University of Texas"; correspondence to Charles Barsotti, 1968-2015 (Box 2782, Folder 7)
  - "High School Reunion"; letters, a program, a drawing, and a certificate, 1990-1999 (Box 2782, Folder 8)
  - "Texas University File"; copies of newspaper articles, newspaper clippings, cartoon printouts, and correspondence (2 folders), 1988-1991 (Box 2782, Folder 9-10)
  - "TX Friends"; correspondence and photos, 1961-2002 (Box 2782, Folder 11)
  - "Barsotti's Restaurant- San Marcos"; photos, copies of the menu, and correspondence, 1987-2005 (Box 2782, Folder 12)
  - Saturday Evening Post checklist on a yellow paper, and a hand-written letter from Ramoth Barsotti, February 2, 2018 (Box 2782, Folder 13)
  - "Saturday Review originals"; two cartoon drawings, March 2014 (Box 2782, Folder 14)
  - "Saturday originals w/clips"; clipping of cartoon drawings from a magazine, and torn out magazine pages with cartoons, 1967-2012 (Box 2782, Folder 15)
  - "SEP"; various newspaper articles, correspondence from The Saturday Evening Post, and a magazine, 1967-1969 (Box 2782, Folder 16)
  - A copy of the front page of The Saturday Evening Post, undated (Box 2782, Folder 17)
  - "Saturday Review, S.R. clips"; correspondence, magazine articles, and magazine clippings of cartoon drawings, 1963-1975 (Box 2782, Folder 18)
  - Post script pages full of cartoon drawings from a magazine, 1962 (Box 2782, Folder 19)
  - "Saturday Evening Post"; a newspaper clipping, correspondence, and a cutout magazine article, 1967-2009 (Box 2782, Folder 20)
  - The Saturday Evening Post, blank post-it notes and blank paper, undated (Box 2782, Folder 21)
  - "Mag. Cartoonists Guild dispute"; correspondence, cartoon drawings, and copies of payment methods, 1968-1973 (Box 2782, Folder 22)
  - "Internal (SEP)"; pages of cartoons and captions for posts, correspondence, and brochures (2 folders), 1968-1981 (Box 2782, Folder 23-24)
  - "SEP correspondence and misc."; correspondence, notes and drawings, 1967-1985 (Box 2782, Folder 25)
  - Copy of The Saturday Evening Post magazine, February 1958 (Box 2782, Folder 26)
  - Mounted list of The Curtis Publishing Company, 1968 (Box 2782, Folder 27)
  - 25 S.E.P. Originals donated to the University of Texas, 1969 (Box 2782, Folder 28)
  - Two copies of The Saturday Evening Post magazine, showing "My Kind of People" cartoon drawings by Charles Barsotti, August 26, 1967 (Box 2783, Folder 1)
  - The Saturday Evening Post magazine, June 15, 1968 (Box 2783, Folder 2)
  - The Saturday Evening Post magazine, with page 92 marked showing "My Kind of People" cartoon by Charles Barsotti, June 15, 1968 (Box 2783, Folder 3)
  - The Saturday Evening Post magazine, with page 84 marked, showing cartoon drawings by Charles Barsotti, January 25, 1969 (Box 2783, Folder 4)
  - Five copies of The Saturday Evening Post magazine, with page 58 marked, showing a cartoon by Charles Barsotti (2 folders), February 8, 1969 (Box 2783, Folder 5-6)
  - The Saturday Evening Post magazine covers, 1968-1969 (Box 2783, Folder 7)
  - The Saturday Evening Post magazine, March 2, 1963 (Box 2783, Folder 8)
  - The Saturday Evening Post magazine, May 6, 1933 (Box 2783, Folder 9)
  - The Saturday Evening Post magazine, November 6, 1915 (Box 2783, Folder 10)
  - The Saturday Evening Post magazine, October 6, 1934 (Box 2783, Folder 11)
  - Two copies of The Saturday Evening Post magazine of Charles Barsotti's cartoons, undated (Box 2783, Folder 12)
  - Cartoon drawings done by Charles Barsotti, 1965-1969 (Box 2783, Folder 13)
  - Two large notebooks filled with cartoon drawings done by Charles Barsotti, 1963-1969 (Box 2784)
- Accession 2018-081
  Additions to cartoonist, Charles Barsotti's collection, 1978-2012. Majority of the materials are letters, magazines, and original artwork. Included in the collection are works submitted and published by Charles Barsotti in Parade Magazine, Fortune Small Business, and Harvard Business Review. There is an original, 1978 Time Magazine with Charles Barsotti's artwork on the cover. The folder titles preceding a semicolon reflect Barsotti's original descriptions.
  - "Harvard Business Review, 4 Published Originals"; Correspondence from Harvard Business Review and including Charles Barsotti's cartoons, August 21, 2007-February 14, 2008 (Box 2808, Folder 1)
  - "Submissions, Harvard Business Review"; Submissions for Harvard Business Review including Charles Barsotti's cartoons, June 21, 2007-October 2, 2008 (Box 2808, Folder 2)
  - "Harvard Business Review Correspondence"; Call for submission for cartoons drawn by Charles Barsotti including magazine, May 23, 2007-February 5, 2009 (Box 2808, Folder 3)
  - "Harvard Business Review, 4 intact magazines"; Four magazines related to Charles Barsotti's work in Harvard Business Review, June-October 2008 (Box 2808, Folder 4)
  - "Parade Correspondence"; Correspondence with Parade Magazine including contract, February 19, 2009-September 6, 2011 (Box 2808, Folder 5)
  - "Parade, 62 Published Originals"; Original cartoon drawings by Charles Barsotti, September 8, 2009-November 30, 2011 (Box 2808, Folder 6)
  - "Parade Magazine, clips and copies of published cartoons"; clips from Parade Magazine of Charles Barsotti's cartoons, May 24, 2009-March 25, 2012 (Box 2808, Folder 7)
  - "FSB"; Fortune Small Business contract and correspondence for cartoonist, Charles Barsotti, July 5, 2006-August 3, 2007 (Box 2808, Folder 8)
  - Fortune Small Business, magazine clips of published cartoons by Charles Barsotti including correspondence and drafts of cartoons, November 2007-April 2008 (Box 2808, Folder 9)
  - Fortune Small Business, five magazines with rough drafts of published cartoons by Charles Barsotti, February-October 2007 (Box 2808, Folder 10)
  - Fortune Small Business Magazine, five magazines with correspondence and rough drafts of Charles Barsotti's published cartoons, September 2006-March 2007 (Box 2808, Folder 11)
  - Fortune Small Business Magazine, four magazines with correspondence and rough drafts of Charles Barsotti's cartoons, April 2007-February 2008 (Box 2808, Folder 12)
  - "Cartoonist Correspondence, Mostly New Yorker"; Various letters and articles saved by Charles Barsotti, 1981-2007 (Box 2808, Folder 13)
  - "Texas Misc"; Miscellaneous Correspondence related to Texas", 1991-2004 (Box 2808, Folder 14)
  - The New Yorker Magazine, Cover drawn by Charles Barsotti, May 15, 1978 (Box 2808, Folder 15)
  - "Humor" Funny articles saved by Charles Barsotti, 2003-2005 (Box 2808, Folder 16)
  - "Tobias"; Various correspondence between Andrew Tobias and Charles Barsotti, 1991-2016 (Box 2808, Folder 17)
- Accession 2018-102
  Archival materials following the last three decades of work from American cartoonist Charles Barsotti of San Marcos, Texas, 1987-2010. Included in the collections are cartoons; product logo concepts; project invoices; and faxes and emails between Barsotti and his clients.
  - "Addison"; Cartoon Invoice, July 30 – August 25, 2005 (Box 2822, Folder 1)
  - "Addison Monsanto"; Monsanto Logos and Correspondence, 1989 (Box 2822, Folder 2)
  - Addison in 1989, Financial Plan, September 1, 1989 – April 3, 1990 (Box 2822, Folder 3)
  - Addison Globe Project"; Invoices and Correspondence, September 29, 1989 - May 8, 1990 (Box 2822, Folder 4)
  - "UK Addison Projects"; Invoices and Correspondences, April 11, 1990 – August 21, 1991 (Box 2822, Folder 5)
  - "Addison Simply Better"; Cartoons, Letters, and Invoices, October 29, 1990 - January 17, 1991 (Box 2822, Folder 6)
  - "Addison Wells Fargo"; Wells Fargo Ads, Magazine, and Letters, December 1991 (Box 2822, Folder 7)
  - "Addison Mallinckrodt Project"; Business Plan, Logo Concepts, and Correspondence, February 1991 (Box 2822, Folder 8)
  - "Newell and Sorrell'; Correspondence, Invoices, and Cartoons, January 2 - October 2, 1992 (Box 2822, Folder 9)
  - "Addison UK Rabobank"; Correspondence and Cartoons, November 14, 1994 - July 4, 1995 (Box 2822, Folder 10)
  - "Newel and Sorrell, Mark Steen, and Hogeschool"; Letters and Hogeschool Concepts, March 5, 1993 – July 2, 1995 (Box 2822, Folder 11)
  - "Hogeschool, Newell and Sorrell"; Cartoons and Letters, November 10, 1994 - May 20, 1997 (Box 2822, Folder 12)
  - "Addison"; Invoices, Cartoons, and Letters, February 23, 1996 – October 22, 1997 (Box 2822, Folder 13)
  - "Tulip Computers - Holland '95"; Pen Sketches, Faxes, and Invoices, July 20 - December 6, 1995 (Box 2822, Folder 14)
  - "Newell + Sorrell, Nederland Project, Steeno"; Faxes, Drawings, and Invoices, February 1 - October 16, 1995 (Box 2822, Folder 15)
  - Photographs from Amsterdam, undated (Box 2822, Folder 16)
  - "Origin/ The Netherlands"; Faxes and Millennium Origin Cartoons, February 13 - June 17, 1998 (Box 2822, Folder 17)
  - "Good Earth International, Tetley Tea"; Coffee, Cookie, and Tea Label Concepts, Emails and Invoices, January 22, 2009 – February 1, 2010 (Box 2822, Folder 18)
  - Addison Around The World, Addison Design Book, October 1989 (Box 2822, Folder 19)
- Accession 2018-136
  Archival material from the noted Saturday Evening Post and The New Yorker cartoonist Charles Barsotti dating 1963-2012. Materials include cartooning project files for various companies. The bulk of the project files consist of correspondence, news clippings, rough and original illustrations, payment invoices and newsletter issues containing illustrations by Barsotti. One oversize box contains large calendars featuring illustrations by Barsotti.
  - "A.A.R.P."; AARP project files, email correspondence, cartoons, payment invoices, facsimiles and illustrator contract, 2005 (Box 2876, Folder 1)
  - "AT&T Della Femina Rothchild Jeary"; AT&T project files, cartoons, correspondence, expense statements, ads, 2001 (Box 2876, Folder 2)
  - "Absolut Vodka Ad"; Absolut Vodka ad campaign cartoons, ads, facsimile correspondence, May-June, 1991 (Box 2876, Folder 3)
  - "The Age-Australia"; The Age, Australian newspaper correspondence and articles, 2004-2005 (Box 2876, Folder 4)
  - "Alter Ego UK Alter Ego"; Alter Ego/British Aerospace Profit Sharing Scheme project files, correspondence, cartoons and payment invoices, January 1997, April 1998 (Box 2876, Folder 5)
  - "Alter Ego British Aerospace – 98"; Alter Ego/British Aerospace Profit Sharing Scheme project files, correspondence profit sharing brochures, rough cartoons, 1998 (Box 2876, Folder 6)
  - "Maurice Wright Atlantis Marketing"; Atlantis Marketing project files, rough cartoons, correspondence, 1992 (Box 2876, Folder 7)
  - "Detritus from Avodart Advert 15 June '07"; Avodart drug ad campaign files, correspondence, rough cartoons, reference photos of park benches, 2007 (Box 2876, Folder 8)
  - "Bill Brewer"; Hallmark birthday card project, correspondence with Bill Brewer artwork-original and photocopy, 2004 (Box 2876, Folder 9)
  - "Blake Dawson Australia"; Blake Dawson Waldron law firm rebranding project, correspondence, project files, rough cartoons, original artwork, payment invoices and contracts, brochures, 2007, 2010 (Box 2876, Folder 10)
  - "Bloomberg"; Bloomberg View project files, screenshots of website with Barsotti illustration, rough cartoons, correspondence, blank invoices, 2012 (Box 2876, Folder 11)
  - "British Telecom Cartoon Bank"; British Telecom internet campaign through The Cartoon Bank, project files, newspaper clippings, correspondence rough cartoons, 1998 (Box 2876, Folder 12)
  - "Boulevard Beer"; Boulevard Brewing Company project files, correspondence, 2005 brewery calendars, original artwork, magazine clippings, 2003-2005 (Box 2876, Folder 13)
  - "Shakespeare Correspondence with Iain Crockart, examples of illustrations from The New Yorker, USA Today and Corporate Wood News, 1982, 1985, 1991 (Box 2876, Folder 14)
  - "Custom Communications"; Custom Communications project files, rough and original illustrations, correspondence, billing statement, artist agreement, one copy of Strategy & Business, 1996 (Box 2876, Folder 15)
  - "CGI–Delphi"; CGI-Delphi project files, billing invoices, correspondence rough cartoons, 1998 (Box 2876, Folder 16)
  - "Celerant Consulting (U.K.) (Cartoon Bank)"; Celerant Consulting project files through Cartoon Bank, rough drawings, correspondence, Celerant booklet, 1998 (Box 2876, Folder 17)
  - "Cystic Fibrosis Found."; Cystic Fibrosis Foundation donated work, correspondence, event trifolds and event booklet with illustrations, 1975 (Box 2876, Folder 18)
  - "Chicago Tribune"; Chicago Tribune artist agreements, correspondence, newspaper clipping with cartoon, 1973, 1975, 1982, 1986 (Box 2876, Folder 19)
  - "Chaney-Nadel Girl Scout Project White Plains"; Chaney-Nadel Girl Scout project files, correspondence, rough and original drawings, finished illustrations, 1986 (Box 2876, Folder 20)
  - "Computer Resources Group"; Computer Resources Group packet folder with Barsotti illustration (2 copies), undated (Box 2876, Folder 21)
  - "Data Warehouse-Ireland"; Data Warehouse IT journal project files, correspondence, rough and original illustrations, copy of journal, billing invoice, 1997 (Box 2877, Folder 1)
  - "DeMarche Assoc."; Holiday greeting cards (6) with Barsotti illustrations for DeMarche Associates, 1981-1983 (Box 2877, Folder 2)
  - "Norwest/Design One 1998"; Integrated Delivery Channels campaign files, rough, original drawings and correspondence (Box 2877, Folder 3)
  - "Design One Bank Am Finis"; Bank of America branch handbook project files, photographs, correspondence, rough drawings, 1993 (Box 2877, Folder 4)
  - "Design One"; Design One project files, correspondence, rough, original drawings, billing invoices, Design One newsletters, 1992-2001 (Box 2877, Folder 5)
  - "Dialog"; Dialog Limited firm correspondence and rough drawing samples pertaining to pharmaceutical company magazine design project, 1994 (Box 2877, Folder 6)
  - "Diner's Club"; Diner's Club newsletter project files, correspondence, articles, rough drawing, 1984 (Box 2877, Folder 7)
  - "Discover Magazine"; Discover magazine project files, articles with Barsotti illustrations, 3 copies of Discover magazine, correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 2877, Folder 8)
  - "Doubletree Hotel Robinson-Thompson-Wise"; Doubletree Hotel restaurant project files, correspondence, rough drawings, 1985 (Box 2877, Folder 9)
  - "Dwell Mag. 2008"; Dwell magazine project files, blank illustration contract, correspondence, IRS W-9 form (Box 2877, Folder 10)
  - "Addison Finished Financial Cookbook"; Addison Financial Cookbook project files, correspondence, rough and original drawings, pay statement, 1992 (Box 2877, Folder 11)
  - "Steeno BUPA"; BUPA project files, correspondence, pay invoice, rough drawings, 2004 (Box 2877, Folder 12)
  - "Boardroom"; Boardroom project files through Bottom Line publications, tax hotline, correspondence, rough and original drawings, 1986, 2004-2005 (Box 2877, Folder 13)
  - "Walt Disney Project with Charlie Podebarac"; Walt Disney project files, original drawing, ToonFest/Missouri, correspondence, 2002-2003, 2005 (Box 2877, Folder 14)
  - "Saturday Evening Post Correspondence Newspaper Clips & Cartoons"; Correspondence, original drawings, newsletters and newspaper clippings pertaining to Barsotti's work for the Saturday Evening Post/Curtis Publishing Company, 1963-1968 (Box 2877, Folder 15)
  - "Addison, Newell & Sorrell, Michael Wolff"; Addison, Newell & Sorrell project files, correspondence with Michael Wolff, original illustrations, roughs, 1991-1992, 2004 (Box 2877, Folder 16)
  - "3i"; Fourth Room and 3i project files, correspondence, rough and original illustrations, billing statements pertaining to Fourth Room Millennium Bug/Y2K project and various 3i design projects, 1968-2008 (Box 2877, Folder 17)
  - "Shakespeare's Globe Theater 3i Globe Theater London"; 3i Globe Theater project files, Shakespeare Festival and Festival of Firsts correspondence, rough, original illustrations, program catalog, 1994, 1997 (Box 2877, Folder 18)
  - "3i"; 3i project files, correspondence, rough drawings and payment statements pertaining to the 3i "Businessman of the Year" ad and 3i calendars, 1991-1994 (Box 2877, Folder 19)
  - "3i"; Correspondence, brochure and rough drawings for the 3i calendar and Christmas card, 1986, 1992 (Box 2877, Folder 20)
  - "3i Calendar"; 3i calendar project files, Correspondence, drawings, payment invoices, 1995-2004 (Box 2877, Folder 21)
  - "3i"; 3i project files, correspondence, rough and original drawings, calendar image thumbnails and pay invoices pertaining the 3i calendar projects, 3i magazine, 3i news and Globe Theater, 1986-1987, 1992, 1995-2008 (Box 2877, Folder 22)
  - 3i 2008 Desk Calendar with cover illustration by Charles Barsotti (Box 2877, Folder 23)
  - "Ralph: A 16-Month Calendar Sept. 1967-Dec. 1968"; Hallmark sixteen-month calendar featuring work by Charles Barsotti, September 1967- December 1968 (Box 2878, Folder 1)
  - "Please Buy This 16 Month Calendar: It's days are Numbered Sept. 1968-Dec. 1969"; Hallmark sixteen-month calendar featuring work by Charles Barsotti, September 1968-December 1969 (Box 2878, Folder 2)
  - "Argus"; Argus Communication project files pertaining to greeting cards and calendars, correspondence, rough and original drawings, purchase orders, cartooning examples and royalty sheets, 1983-1985, 1987 (Box 2878, Folder 3)
  - "EBay Cartoon Bank"; EBay project files through The New Yorker Cartoon Bank correspondence and rough drawings, undated (Box 2878, Folder 4)
  - "Eisner"; Eisner project files, correspondence, pay invoice, rough and original drawings, purchase order, 2003 (Box 2878, Folder 5)
  - "Espree"; Espree magazine project files, correspondence, magazine issues publishing contract agreement, 2001-2005 (Box 2878, Folder 6)
  - "Fast Time"; Fast Times payment statement, 1996 (Box 2878, Folder 7)
  - "Jay Fielden"; Correspondence and rough drawings, 1999 (Box 2878, Folder 8)
  - "Folly Theater KCMO"; Two invitations for a Folly Theater, Kansas City, Missouri event with illustration by Charles Barsotti, 1982 (Box 2878, Folder 9)
  - "Food Store 1993"; Food Store café project files, correspondence, business plan, original rough drawings (Box 2878, Folder 10)
  - "Gallup"; Gallup project files, correspondence, rough drawings, 1997, 1999 (Box 2878, Folder 11)
  - "German Calendar"; Der neue Raben Kalender 2012 project, correspondence, sample cartoons, 2011 (Box 2878, Folder 12)
  - "Der neue Raben Kalender fur jenden Tag im Jahr 2012"; 2012 German calendar with an illustration by Charles Barsotti (Box 2878, Folder 12a)
  - "German Project Didn't Go"; Michael Conrad & Leo Burnett German ad agency project, correspondence, rough drawings, 1994, 2010 (Box 2878, Folder 13)
  - "Good Housekeeping"; Good Housekeeping project files, correspondence, rough drawings, 2010 (Box 2878, Folder 14)
  - "Google Project 2007"; Google project files, correspondence, rough and original drawings, content license, non-disclosure agreements, 2007, 2009 (Box 2878, Folder 15)
  - "Gourmet Online Cartoon"; Gourmet Live online magazine culinary cartoon project files, correspondence, rough drawings, invoice and contract, 2010-2011 (Box 2878, Folder 16)
  - "Guido's Triangle Vespa"; Guido's Triangle Vespa ad campaign, ad with Barsotti cartoon, undated (Box 2878, Folder 17)
  - "Hallmark Correspondence"; Hallmark greeting card and calendar project files, contract agreement, correspondence, rough drawings, copyright registration, 1971, 1974-1975 (Box 2878, Folder 18)
  - "Hallmark Friend Correspondence"; Correspondence from friends, Hallmark pay stub, 1968, 1981, 1983, 1993 (Box 2878, Folder 19)
  - "Hallmark"; Hallmark project files pertaining to greeting card design, correspondence, cards illustrated by Barsotti, Hallmark freelancer info packets, purchase invoices for projects, 1975-1995 (Box 2878, Folder 20)